truvo.com 2009-08-08

# Privacy policy - Truvo

Effective as from April 20, 2009

Users of www.truvo.com, www.truvo.be and www.truvo.pt:

Truvo Belgium Comm.V., located at Keyserlei 5 bus 7, 2018 Antwerpen, Belgium (" **Truvo** "), is committed to protecting your privacy and to comply with the applicable data protection and privacy laws. Truvo is the controller of the personal data of the persons who register with the website and the affiliated websites located at www.truvo.be (collectively, the " **Site** ") and will process the personal data of its registered users in accordance with the Law of 8 December 1992 on the protection of personal privacy as regards the processing of personal data _(Wet tot bescherming van de persoonlijke levenssfeer ten opzichte van de verwerking van persoonsgegevens/Loi relative à la protection de la vie privée à l'égard des traitements de données à caractère personnel)_. 

Users of www.truvo.ie:

Truvo Ireland Limited located at St. Martin’s House, Waterloo Road, Dublin 4, Ireland (" **Truvo** "), is committed to protecting your privacy and to complying with Irish data protection and privacy legislation. Truvo is the controller of the personal data of persons who register and/or use with the website and the affiliated website located at www.truvo.ie (the " **Site** "). 

BY USING THE SITE, YOU EXPRESSLY AGREE TO THE PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THESE TERMS, YOU SHOULD NOT REGISTER TO OR USE THE SITE. 

Truvo may share the personal data of its registered users with its subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control (collectively, " **Affiliates** ") that it may have now or in the future, in which case Truvo will require them to honour this Privacy Policy. In addition, Truvo may disclose personal data to any prospective buyer of any business or assets related to the Site or of all or any part of the business or assets of Truvo. 

Truvo commits to take all commercially reasonable measures to ensure that the collection of personal data is limited to what is necessary to fulfil the purposes identified below. If Truvo should wish to use your personal data for other purposes than for which they were collected, Truvo will ask you for your consent prior to such use. 

## Account information

If you create an account to take advantage of the full range of services offered on the Site, Truvo asks for and records your personal information such as your name and e-mail address. 

## Submissions

Truvo stores and may publicly display your submissions on the Site in order to provide its services. The term "submissions" refers to the information that you submit to or post on the Site for public display, such as business ratings, reviews, photos, comments, and the information that you display as part of your account profile. Your submissions may be published together with your account name. When making any submissions you are responsible for ensuring that no personal data of any third party is included unless you have checked that the relevant third party consents to you providing us with this information and you have brought this Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions of the Site to their attention prior to submitting their data. 

## Feedback

If you contact Truvo to provide feedback, register a complaint, or ask a question, Truvo may record any personal information and other content that you provide in your communication so that it can effectively respond to your communication. 

## Personal messaging

In order to allow registered users to send and receive personal messages to other registered users of the Site, Truvo will record all the messages that are sent and received by using the Site's personal messaging feature. 

## Activity

Truvo may record information relating to your use of the Site, such as the number of searches undertaken, the number of pages viewed, your browser type, IP address, requested URL, referring URL, and timestamp information. Truvo uses this type of information to administer the Site and provide the highest possible level of service to its users. Truvo also uses this information to perform statistical analyses of its users’ behaviour and characteristics in order to measure the interest in and the use of the various areas of the Site. Users cannot be identified individually as a result thereof. 

## Cookies

Truvo sends cookies to the computer of its registered users in order to uniquely identify their browser and improve the quality of the service. The term "cookies" refers to small pieces of information that a website sends to a computer's hard drive while the Site is visited. Truvo may use both session cookies (which expire once the browser is closed) and persistent cookies (which stay on a computer until they are deleted). Persistent cookies can be removed by following the help file directions in the internet browser. If the cookies are disabled or deleted, some areas of the Site may not work properly or at all. 

## Enforcement

Truvo may use the information collected in connection with your use of the Site (including your personal information) in order to investigate, enforce, and apply its Terms & Conditions and Privacy Policy. 

## Direct Marketing

Truvo may use your personal information to inform you about its products and services where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes. 

## Changes to Privacy Policy

Truvo may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time and any changes will be posted on this page. You should visit this page from time to time to review such changes and your continued use of the Site shall constitute your consent to all such changes.

## Access to, Rectification of, and Objections to use of Personal Information

You have a right to access your personal information held by Truvo and to have any inaccurate information rectified. In addition, you may contact Truvo at any time to object to the use of your personal information for the purposes of direct marketing. 

Users of www.truvo.com, www.truvo.be and www.truvo.pt:  
If you wish to contact us regarding your personal information please e-mail us at feedback@truvo.be or write to us at Keyserlei 5 bus 7, 2018 Antwerpen, Belgium. 

You can also direct yourself to the Belgian Privacy Commission (Commissie voor de bescherming van de persoonlijke levenssfeer/Commission de la protection de la vie privée), Hoogstraat 139, 1000 Brussel, tel. 02/213.85.40, fax. 02/213.85.65, e-mail: commission@privacycommission.be. 

Users of www.truvo.ie:  
If you wish to contact us regarding your personal information please e-mail us at feedback@truvo.ie or write to us at St. Martin’s House, Waterloo Road, Dublin 4.
